oakfurnitureland.co.uk 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy: Shop with confidence at Oak Furniture Land

## YOUR INFORMATION AND HOW WE PROTECT IT

WHO WE ARE

In this privacy policy, “we”, “us” and “our” refers to Oak Furniture Land. References to “our website” or “the website” are to www.oakfurnitureland.co.uk.

THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

The information we collect via the website may include: 

  * Any personal details you knowingly provide via forms or email; such as name, address, telephone number etc. 
  * Your preferences and use of email updates, recorded by emails we send you (if you select to receive email updates on products and offers). 
  * Your IP Address - this is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on the website. This information is used to monitor your usage of the website. 

Data recorded by the website helps us to remember your preferred settings; this saves you from re-entering information on return visits to the site. Such data is recorded locally on your computer through the use of cookies. Most browsers can be programmed to reject, or warn you before downloading cookies, information regarding this may be found in your browser’s ‘help’ facility. 

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the **Data Protection Act 1998** and other applicable laws. The details we collect will be used: 

  * To process your order, to provide after-sales service (we may pass your details to another organisation to supply/deliver products or services you have purchased and/or to provide after-sales service). 
  * In certain cases we may use your email address to send you information on our other products and services. In such a case you will be offered the option to opt in/out before completing your purchase. We do not send random marketing emails to personal email addresses (spam). 
  * Once subscribed to our email offers, you can unsubscribe if you so wish but we will not share your data with third parties unless authorised by yourself to do so. 
  * We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the website and issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes. 

YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to request a copy of any information that we currently hold about you. In order to receive such information please send your contact details including address and payment of £10 to cover administration expenses to the following address: 

Privacy  
Oakfurnitureland   
Unit DC2  
South Marston Industrial Estate   
Swindon   
SN3 4TN

OTHER WEBSITES

This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours.
